windustry.org 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy - Windustry

Windustry appreciates your support and is dedicated to protecting your privacy.

### Information Collection 

Windustry's website collects some non-identifying basic information when you visit. The site tracks the total number of individuals viewing each page including hits and visits. Windustry uses this information to improve the website through content and design management. the statistics gathered do not contain personally identifiable information.

### Information Sharing

Windustry does not sell, share, trade, or rent personal information with third parties. Information related to donations are aggregate statistics that do not include personally identifiable information and may be shared with a third party. This includes the total number of donors and the total amount of donations for various periods of time.

Please note that Windustry's public forums may be used in Windustry's marketing materials. Information that is disclosed on these areas becomes public information so please be cautious when providing personal information on these networks.

### Links

Please note that the links that are listed on Windustry's website contain their own privacy policies. Windustry recommends reviewing these policies prior to submitting personal information, as their policies may differe from Windustry's policy.

### Privacy Policy Updates

Windustry reserves the right to update the privacy policy at any time. Updates will be posted on the website, at which time they become effective immediately.

### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.windustry.org/contact). We will be happy to further explain our policy and the donation system.
